Guide to the Fales Manuscript Collection circa 1700-2000 MSS.001
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Letter sized boxes
  - Joyce, James: Pound, Ezra [transcription, unsigned, of a letter re Ulysses, 1922] [item (photocopy) removed - see Collection Files], undated (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Joyce, James: U.S. Attorney on Ulysses, Dec. 12, 1933 [photocopy] (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Joyce, James: Reviews, undated (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Joyce, James: Budgen, Frank [A.L.s re F.W. painting], undated (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Joyce, James: Memorabilia, 1) Brick, from Clongows School; 2) Wood, from Belvedere College, undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Kantor, MacKinlay, undated (Box 100, Folder 1a)
  - Kavanagh, Julia, undated (Box 100, Folder 1b)
  - Kaye, Francis R.R., undated (Box 100, Folder 1c)
  - Kaye-Smith, Shiela (1887-1956), undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Kazin, Alfred, undated (Box 100, Folder 3a)
  - Keeble, Robert (1887-1927), undated (Box 100, Folder 3b)
  - Kean, Charles (1811-1868), undated (Box 100, Folder 3c)
  - Kean, Ellen (1815-1880), undated (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Kean, John (senator), undated (Box 100, Folder 3e)
  - Keane, P., undated (Box 100, Folder 4a)
  - Keeley, Mary Ann (Goward) (1805-1899), undated (Box 100, Folder 4b)
  - Keller, Helen (1880-1968), undated (Box 100, Folder 4c)
  - Kelly, Robert: Matter 1-4, edited by R.K., 1964-1965? (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - [Kelsey, Dallas: see Kenmare, Dallas, Box 100], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_d5717e97bddcdb0a9e95e2ef3f40d84b)
  - Kemble, Fanny (Frances Anne Kemble) (Mrs. Pierce Butler) (1809-1893), undated (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Kemble, Fanny (Frances Anne Kemble) (Mrs. Pierce Butler) (1809-1893): Libel for Divorce; includes A.L.s, undated (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Kenmare, Dallas (pseud. of Dallas Kenmare Browne Kelsey), undated (Box 100, Folder 8a)
  - Kennan, George F. (1845-1924), undated (Box 100, Folder 8b)
  - Kennedy, Charles Rann (1871-1950), undated (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy, Charles Rann (1871-1950): MS. The Terrible Meek, undated (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Kennedy, John Pendleton (1795-1870), undated (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Kennedy, Margaret (1896- ), undated (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Kent, Ann, undated (Box 100, Folder 13a)
  - Kent, Charles (1823-1902), undated (Box 100, Folder 13b)
  - Kent, Rockwell (1882- ), undated (Box 100, Folder 13c)
  - Kenyon, George Kenyon (2nd Baron) (1776-1855), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 1)
  - Kernahan, Coulson (1858- ), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 2)
  - Kerouac, Jack (1922-1969), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 3)
  - Kester, Paul (1870-1933), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 4a)
  - Key, Francis Scott (1779-1843), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 4b)
  - Keynes, Geoffrey Langdon (1877- ), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 5a)
  - Keynes, John Maynard (1883- ), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 5b)
  - Kilmer, Alfred Joyco (1886-1918): 1 A.L.s.; 10 commentaries on students' poems, undated (Box 100.5, Folder 6)
  - King, Basil (1859-1928), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 7a)
  - King, Charles (1844-1933), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 7b)
  - King, W. V. S. R., undated (Box 100.5, Folder 7c)
  - King, Edward (1735-1807), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 8a)
  - King, Grace Elizabeth (1851-1932), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 8b)
  - King, Horatio (1811-1897), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 8c)
  - King, Rosa Eleanor (1865- ), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 8)
  - King, Rufus (1893- ), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 9a)
  - King Hall, Magdelen, undated (Box 100.5, Folder 9b)
  - Kingsley, Charles (1819-1875), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 10)
  - Kingsley, Frances Eliza (1841-1891), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 11a)
  - Kingsley, Henry (1830-1876), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 11b)
  - Kingsley, Mary Henriette (1862-1900), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 11c)
  - Kinnay, Thomas T., undated (Box 100.5, Folder 11)
  - Kinnell, Galway, undated (Box 100.5, Folder 12)
  - Kipling, Rudyard: Correspondence, 1894-1935 (Box 100.5, Folder 13)
  - Kipling, Rudyard: Photocopies, 1894-1935; undated (Box 100.5, Folder 14)
  - Kipling, Rudyard: Miscellaneous [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 100.5, Folder 15)
  - Kirk, Ellen Warner (1842- ), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 16a)
  - Knight, Daniel Ridgeway (1840-1924), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 16b)
  - Knight, G. Wilson, undated (Box 100.5, Folder 16c)
  - Knowles, James, Sir (1831-1908), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 16)
  - Knowles, James Sheridan (1784-1862), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 16e)
  - Knox, Ronald A. (1888-1957): 2 A.L.s., undated (Box 100.5, Folder 17)
  - Koestler, Arthur, undated (Box 100.5, Folder 18a)
  - Kolodin, Irving, undated (Box 100.5, Folder 18b)
  - Komroff, Manuel (1890- ), undated (Box 100.5, Folder 18c)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy: Interview w/ Jerome Klinkowitz, undated (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy: Interview w/ Jerome Klinkowitz, undated (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy: Interview w/ Jerome Klinkowitz [1st Transcript], undated (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy: Interview w/ Jerome Klinkowitz, undated (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy: Interview w/ Jerome Klinkowitz [1st Draft], undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy: Atlantic Monthly, undated (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy, undated (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy: Fiction International, undated (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy: Interview w/ Jerome Klinkowitz, Betrayed by Jerzy Kosinski, undated (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy: Klinkowitz Preface to Article for Fiction International, undated (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy, undated (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Kraft, Isabelle: [w/A.N.s. by George Sand, August 13, 1866] (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Kramer, Aaron: MS., undated (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Kramer, Aaron: Writings in translation, undated (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Krummacher, F. W. (Friedrich Wilhelm) (1796-1868), undated (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Kryss, T. L. (Tom L.): MS. Dialogue in Blue [paste up], undated (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Kuhn, A. K.: autograph of Rutherford B. Hayes, undated (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - [L.E.L. (Landon, Letitia Elizabeth): see Landon, Letitia Elizabeth, Box 104], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_597b1ba59d996b6819864807c3a3e7e8)
  - LaBelle, Christine: MS. [20 pieces], undated (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - LaBelle, Christine: MS. Notebook: poems from Alfalfa Wild, The Difference Between, etc., undated (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Ladd, Henry, undated (Box 103, Folder 3a)
  - Lafarge, John, undated (Box 103, Folder 3b)
  - La Farge, Oliver (1901-1963), undated (Box 103, Folder 3c)
  - Laidlaw, William (1780-1845) (Sir Walter Scott's steward), undated (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Laing, Alexander K. (1903- ), undated (Box 103, Folder 5a)
  - Laing, John W., undated (Box 103, Folder 5b)
  - LaMartine, Alphonse Marie-Louise de, undated (Box 103, Folder 5c)
  - LaMaziere, Pierre (1879- ), undated (Box 103, Folder 6a)
  - Lambert, Hilda Orr, undated (Box 103, Folder 6b)
  - Lammon, Joseph (1811-1874), undated (Box 103, Folder 6c)
  - [Landon, Letitia Elizabeth: see Box 104], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_298007035439a7db1ffab2ce5432fa0b)
  - Landor, Walter Savage, undated (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Landsdowne, Henry Petty FitzMaurice, 3rd Marquis (1780-1863), undated (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Landseer, Thomas (1795-1880), undated (Box 103, Folder 9a)
  - Lane, John (1854-1920), undated (Box 103, Folder 9b)
  - Landon, Letitia Elizabeth (1802-1838): Correspondence I [9 pieces], undated (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Landon, Letitia Elizabeth (1802-1838): Correspondence II [8 pieces], undated (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Landon, Letitia Elizabeth (1802-1838): Correspondence III [7 pieces], undated (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Landon, Letitia Elizabeth (1802-1838): Correspondence IV [6 pieces], undated (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Landon, Letitia Elizabeth (1802-1838): Correspondence V [6 pieces], undated (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Landon, Letitia Elizabeth (1802-1838): MS. I, undated (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Landon, Letitia Elizabeth (1802-1838): MS. II: The Royal Marriage [includes letter to Mr. Shobert], undated (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Lang, Andrew (1844-1912): Correspondence [1886-1907] (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Lang, Andrew (1844-1912): Correspondence [1908-1910; undated] (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Lang, Andrew (1844-1912): Correspondence [undated] (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Lang, Andrew (1844-1912): Correspondence [undated] (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Lang, Andrew (1844-1912): Correspondence [undated] (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Lang, Andrew (1844-1912): Correspondence [undated] (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Lang, Andrew (1844-1912): Correspondence [undated] (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Lang, Andrew (1844-1912): Correspondence [undated] (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Lang, Andrew (1844-1912): Bound Volume of Correspondence, undated (Box 105, Folder 8b)
  - Lang, Andrew (1844-1912): Bound Volume of Correspondence, undated (Box 105, Folder 8c)
  - Lang, Andrew (1844-1912): MS., undated (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Lang, Andrew (1844-1912): Times Obituary, July 22, 1912 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Lang, Anton, undated (Box 106, Folder 1a)
  - Lanier, Henry Wysham (1875- ), undated (Box 106, Folder 1b)
  - Lanier, Sidney (1842-1881), undated (Box 106, Folder 1c)
  - Larcom, Lucy (1824-1893), undated (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Lardner, Ring (1885-1933), undated (Box 106, Folder 3a)
  - Lasker, Emanuel (1868-1941), undated (Box 106, Folder 3b)
  - Laski, Harold J., undated (Box 106, Folder 3c)
  - Laski, Mary L., undated (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Lathrop, George Parsons (1851-1898), undated (Box 106, Folder 5a)
  - Lathrop, Rose Hawthorne (1851-1926), undated (Box 106, Folder 5b)
  - [not assigned], 1690-2000 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Latimer, Elizabeth Wormeley (1822-1904), undated (Box 106, Folder 7a)
  - Lavater, Johann Kasper (1741-180?), undated (Box 106, Folder 7b)
  - Laver, James (1899- ), undated (Box 106, Folder 7c)
  - Lawless, Hon. Emily (1845-1913), undated (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Lawrence, Lady Anne: 1 A.L.s. Sept 1939? re Sir Alexander Lawrence's death; 1 Miscellaneous, undated (Box 106, Folder 7e)
  - Lawrence, D. H. (David Herbert) (1885-1930): MS. Psychoanalysis and the Unconsious [with autograph corrections], undated (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Lawrence, D. H. (David Herbert) (1885-1930): Miscellaneous: Dust Jacket to F. Carter's; D. H. Lawrence and the Body Mystical; London Archer, 1932 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Lawrence, Harry, undated (Box 106, Folder 10a)
  - Lawrence, Samuel, undated (Box 106, Folder 10b)
  - Lawrence, Thomas Edward (1888-1935), undated (Box 106, Folder 10c)
  - Layard, Austen Henry, Sir (1817-1894), undated (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Lea, Henry Charles (1825-1909), undated (Box 106, Folder 11a)
  - Leacock, Stephen (1869-1944), undated (Box 106, Folder 11b)
  - Leadbeaten, Mary Shakleton (1758-1826), undated (Box 106, Folder 12a)
  - Lean, Florence (Marryat) Church (1837-1899), undated (Box 106, Folder 12b)
  - Lecocq, Charles A (1832- ), undated (Box 106, Folder 12c)
  - Lee, Mrs.: Mat. The Night Alarm, undated (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Lee, Mrs. Hannah Farnham (Sawyer) (1780-1865), undated (Box 106, Folder 14a)
  - Lee, Laurie, undated (Box 106, Folder 14b)
  - Lee, Sidney, Sir (1859-1926), undated (Box 106, Folder 14c)
  - Leech, John (1817-1864): Letters and Drawings, undated (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Leech, John (1817-1864), undated (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Leed, H. E., Rev., undated (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - LeFanu, Joseph Sheridan (1814-1873), undated (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Lefranc, A., undated (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): Le Gallienne, Eva, undated (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): Le Gallienne, Gwendolyn, undated (Box 107, Folder 2a)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): Le Gallienne, Hesper, undated (Box 107, Folder 2b)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): Correspondence to A - K, undated (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): Correspondence to Bennett, Arthur [Booklovers' Club], undated (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): Correspondence to Griffith, William, undated (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): Correspondence to L, undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): Correspondence Printed; Marriage and Death Notice [Mildred Le Gallienne]; Miscellaneous, undated (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): Correspondence to M - Z; unidentified, undated (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): Correspondence [unidentified], undated (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): Correspondence to R.L.G., undated (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. Album Dedications to R.L.G., undated (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. The Book-Bills of Narcissus, undated (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. A Borrowed Sovereign; Cyril Leicester; Dear Dead Women, undated (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. Do You Ever Get Tired Running the Train, undated (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. The Eclipse of God, undated (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. English Poems, undated (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. English Poems [printed], undated (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. The First Church of the Restoration, American, undated (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. The Gentleman Martyrs, undated (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. George Meredith, Some Characteristics, undated (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. How to Read Poetry; The Land of Children Unforgot; The Land of Lost Faces, undated (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. The Laurel of Gossip; The Lord Christ Came to Notre Dame; The Meander of Broken Hearts; Romance of the Map of America; The Shadow of the Rose [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. The Wandering Home; Omni-Bussing; The Case of the Plain Man, undated (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. 31 Mats., undated (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. Miscellaneous, undated (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. Miscellaneous and Fragments, undated (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): MS. Publications, Essays, Etc., undated (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Le Gallienne, Richard (1866-1947): Minutes of the Book Lovers' Club [bound notebook], undated (Box 108, Folder 8a)
  - MSS: A Copy of Verses; My Ladies' Sonnets; Signor Benoni's Violin Playing; Travels in England; Proofs: Quest for the Golden Boy, undated (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Lehmann, Rosamund (1903- ), undated (Box 110, Folder 1a)
  - Leigh, Augusta (Byron), undated (Box 110, Folder 1b)
  - Leighton, Clara Veronica Hope (1900- ), undated (Box 110, Folder 2a)
  - Leighton, Frederick, Lord (1830-1896), undated (Box 110, Folder 2b)
  - Lejmska, Ethel, undated (Box 110, Folder 2c)
  - Leland, Charles G. (1824-1903), undated (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Lemon, Mark (1809-1870), undated (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Lennox, Charles (1735-1806): 1 A.L.s., undated (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Lenski, Lois, undated (Box 110, Folder 5a)
  - Leon, Charles, undated (Box 110, Folder 5b)
  - Leontief, Estelle, undated (Box 110, Folder 5c)
  - LeQueux, William (1864-1927), undated (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Leslie, Frank, undated (Box 110, Folder 7a)
  - Leslie, Sir Shane, bart. (1885- ), undated (Box 110, Folder 7b)
  - Lettsom, William Nansom (1796-1865), undated (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Lever, Charles James (1806-1872), undated (Box 110, Folder 9a)
  - Lever, Samuel, undated (Box 110, Folder 9b)
  - Leverson, Ada, undated (Box 110, Folder 10a)
  - Leverson, Ernest W., undated (Box 110, Folder 10b)
  - [Levertov, Denise: see Box 111], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_f1526a76343e65a8ae79d6956b1f61db)
  - Levin, Meyer: [see also Box 112 for MS. The Fanatic], undated (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Lewes, George Henry (1817-1878), undated (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Lewis, Agnes (Smith) (1843-1926), undated (Box 110, Folder 13a)
  - Lewis, Alfred H. (1857-1914), undated (Box 110, Folder 13b)
  - Lewis, Clive Staples (1898- ), undated (Box 110, Folder 13c)
  - [Lewis, Harry: see Box 113], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_f113b9536335f21ca7dddec8a51c889e)
  - Lewis, John Frederick: MS. Imported Brass, undated (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Lewis, Sinclair: Correspondence [1907-1934] [see also Legal Size for Proofs of Four Days on the Webutuck River] (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Lewis, Windham, undated (Box 110, Folder 16a)
  - Liddell Hart, Basil Henry, undated (Box 110, Folder 16b)
  - Liddon, Henry P. (1829-1890), undated (Box 110, Folder 16c)
  - Lieber, Francis (1800-1872), undated (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Lindley, Jay, undated (Box 110, Folder 17a)
  - Lindsay, A. D., undated (Box 110, Folder 17b)
  - Lindsay, Jack, undated (Box 110, Folder 17c)
  - Lingard, John (1771-1851), undated (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Linklater, Eric (1899- ), undated (Box 110, Folder 17e)
  - Linklater, Eric (1899- ): Notebook [MS. A Year of Space], undated (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Linton, Elizabeth Lynn (1822-1898), undated (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Lion, Leon M., undated (Box 110, Folder 20a)
  - [Lionni, Paolo: see Box 114], 1690-2000 (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_83194f407aea18e9cdef3badb33ed7d1)
  - Lippincott, Sara Jane (Clarke) (1823-1904) (Grace Greenwood, pseud.), undated (Box 110, Folder 20b)
  - Lippman, Walter (1889- ), undated (Box 110, Folder 20c)
  - Little, W.J. Knox, undated (Box 110, Folder 21a)
  - Liverpool, Charles Jenkinson, 1st Earl (1727-1808), undated (Box 110, Folder 21b)
  - Liverpool, Robert Banks Jenkinson, 2d Earl (1770-1828), undated (Box 110, Folder 21c)
  - Llewellyn, R. A., undated (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Levertov, Denise: [Photocopies] [Originals in Caterpillar Archives], undated (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Levertov, Denise: Love; Origin; Miscellaneous [Photocopies] [Original in specific archives], undated (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Levin, Meyer: MS. The Fanatic, undated (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 1: from Allen, Donald; Antin, David, undated (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 2: from Banks, Russell, undated (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 3: from Berge´, Carol; Corman, Cid; Creeley, Robert, undated (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 4: from Enslin, Theodore, 1965-1966 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 5: from Enslin, Theodore, 1967-1971 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 6: from Eshleman, Clayton [see also Angel Hair and Legal Folders: Spurious Poem; Music Recessional], undated (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 7: from Finlay, Ian Hamilton; Fraser, Kathleen, undated (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 8: from Ginsberg, Allen [MS. Fragment from The Fall of America], undated (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 9: from Greene, Jonathan, undated (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 10: from Grossinger, Richard and Lindy Hough, undated (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 11: from Hollo, Anselm, undated (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 12: from Ignatow, David; Kelly, Robert; Kraf, Elaine; LaBelle, Christine; Locke, Duane, undated (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 13: from Lowenfells, Walter; Lowinshon, Ronald; Marshall, Jack, undated (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 14: from McClure, Michael; MacLow, Jackson, undated (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 15: from Oppenheimer, Joel; Ossman, David, undated (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 16: from Randall, Margaret [see also El Corno], undated (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 17: from Schwerner, Arnold; Sinclair, John, undated (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Lewis, Harry: Correspondence 18: from Vas Dias, Robert [1 A.L.s.]; Wakosky, Diane; Zukovsky, Louis [10 pcs.], undated (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - Lewis, Harry: H.L., Ed. [and Wakoski, Diane]: MS. Software, undated (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - Lionni, Paolo (1938- ): [East Village School]: Checklist, undated (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Lionni, Paolo (1938- ): [East Village School]: Correspondence MS. A - B, undated (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Lionni, Paolo (1938- ): [East Village School]: Correspondence MS. C - D, undated (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Lionni, Paolo (1938- ): [East Village School]: Correspondence MS. E - F, undated (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Lionni, Paolo (1938- ): [East Village School]: Correspondence MS. G, undated (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Lionni, Paolo (1938- ): [East Village School]: Correspondence MS. H - K, undated (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Lionni, Paolo (1938- ): [East Village School]: Correspondence MS. L - N, undated (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Lionni, Paolo (1938- ): [East Village School]: Correspondence MS. R - T, undated (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Lionni, Paolo (1938- ): [East Village School]: Correspondence MS. W, undated (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Lionni, Paolo (1938- ): [East Village School]:, undated (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Lionni, Paolo (1938- ): [East Village School]: Pictorial, Robert Branaman, undated (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Locke, D.R., undated (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Locke, Duane: 1 A.L.s.; MS. From the Bottom of the Sea, undated (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Locke, William John (1863-1930): Correspondence, undated (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Locke, William John (1863-1930): Miscellaneous [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Locke, William John (1863-1930), undated (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Locker-Lampson, Frederick (1821-1865), undated (Box 115, Folder 6a)
  - Lockhart, Charlotte Sophia (Scott) (1799-1837) (wife of John, daughter of Sir Walter), undated (Box 115, Folder 6b)
  - Lockhart, John Gibson (1794-1854), undated (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot (1850-1924), undated (Box 115, Folder 8a)
  - Lodge, Oliver Joseph, Sir (1851-1940), undated (Box 115, Folder 8b)
  - Logan, Stanley, undated (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Lomax, John Avery (1872-1948), undated (Box 115, Folder 10a)
  - Londesborough, undated (Box 115, Folder 10b)
  - London, Charmian Kittredge, undated (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - London, Jack: Correspondence, undated (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - London, Jack: Pictorial; Miscellaneous, undated (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - London Letter, undated (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Long, John Luther (1861-1927), undated (Box 115, Folder 15a)
  - Longfellow, Alice M., undated (Box 115, Folder 15b)
  - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth (1807-1882): Correspondence [1837-1870] (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth (1807-1882): Correspondence [1872-1882] (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth (1807-1882): Mats and Miscellaneous, undated (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Longfellow, Samuel (1819-1892), undated (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Longman, Charles James (1852-1934), undated (Box 115, Folder 20a)
  - Longworth, Maria The´rese (1832-1881), undated (Box 115, Folder 20b)
  - Lonsdale, William [see also Legal Size], undated (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Loos, Anita, undated (Box 115, Folder 22)
  - Lord, Eleazar (1788-1871): von Lennep, E.J. 2 A.L.s.; McCombs, Nelson (Asst Librarian, N.Y.U.), undated (Box 115, Folder 23)
  - Lorenz, Lincoln, undated (Box 115, Folder 24a)
  - Lorimer, Louise, undated (Box 115, Folder 24b)
  - Lossing, John Benson, undated (Box 115, Folder 24c)
  - Lothrop, Harriett Mulford Stone (1844-1924) (Margaret Sidney, pseud.), undated (Box 115, Folder 25a)
  - Lovelace, Augusta Ada (Byron) (1815-1852), undated (Box 115, Folder 25b)